Braden T. Clapp bradenclapp@gmail.com

(541)663-6005 221 W 5th Cheney, WA 99004

Skills

3 years of Java and HTML/CSS programming. 1 year of C programming. Experience creating console based applications. Proved programming proficiency by passing the A.P.E provided by EWU. Experience using Unix and Windows based systems. Ability to implement design patterns and create UMLs. 4 years of Adobe application experience including Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, and InDesign. Passionate about learning new programming skills and languages.

Projects

- Client-Server based Tic-Tac-Toe game with graphics
- Sales report comprised by mySQL database and formatted by Java
- Dungeon crawler game made to implement design patterns
- Secure Coding program used in attack/defend scenario
- Multiple client chat server

Education

Eastern Washington University, Cheney, WA, Fall 2012 - Present Bachelor of Arts, Computer Science Expected graduation: Winter 2016

Eastern Oregon University, La Grande, OR, Fall 2010- Spring 2012 Media Arts, General Education

Work Experience

Brent Clapp Media Services, La Grande, OR, 2008 - Present

- Recorded events and scanned pictures for clients.
- Converted old media to present media formats.
- Assembled and packed equipment for productions.

Albertsons 2008 - 2012, La Grande, OR, 2008-2012

- Worked as a Cashier entering codes and scanning groceries.
- Interacted with customers and provided service.
- Stocked shelves
- Handled transactions